原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译   千只鹤飞过波千鸟  tong大梨
翻译   AlgerDestiny  五天  Stampy  VC
翻译   二糯米  马丁马丁回音山  不见紧张
校对     屯栗子
时间轴     兜兜兜爹
后期     渔夫
总监     屯栗子
辛普森一家
第三十一季  第二十一集
你好大哥  看看你的信箱
Hey there chief. Look at your mail box,
几周都没清理了
it hasn't been emptied for weeks.
别啊  别是信箱
Oh no... not the mail.
万一我错过了优惠券使用期限
What if I'm missing out on coupon packs,
或是法院传票  可咋办
or perhaps a jury summons?
没了信件  我怎么活啊
How will I live without my paper e-mails?
行了我懂了
Eh, I get it.
但是拜托配合一下  理理干净
But be a pal, pally. Empty it out.
它已经晒了一段时间日光浴
Hmm, it has been baking in the sun for a while.
我觉得可
I think it's done.
烘信卷
Mail loaf!
切开烘信卷  好好切开它
Carve that mail. Carve it good.
最后一块谁想要
Who wants an end piece?
我被邀请去阿迪家参加生日派对
I'm invited to a birthday party at Addy's.
阿迪  我不知道你有这个朋友  她教什么科目
Addy? I don't know that friend. What subject does she teach?
是个小朋友
It's a kid!
我认识一些小朋友  那是个阿迪家的睡衣派对
I know kids. It's a sleepover at Addy's house.
阿迪  记得图书馆吗
Addy! Remember the library?
图书馆马姬
Library Marge.
我们是唯一喜欢那套旧书《赛马女孩》的人
We were the only ones who loves this old series of books Gallop Girls.
旧书的味道
Mmm, old book smell.
新朋友的味道
Mmm, new friend smell.
女孩子跟马之间到底怎么回事
What is the deal with girls and horses?
是不是因为男孩子拿走了所有的好动物
Is it 'cause boys took all the good animals,
比如狗狗和忍者
like dogs and ninjas?
马是大自然的凯旋
Horses are nature's triumph.
他们完美结合了力量
They have the perfect combination of power,
优雅和能编辫子的毛发
grace and braidable hair.
蠢蠢蠢  傻  一二三不准动
Dumb, dumb, stupid. Legs don't move.
呕  粉的
Ew. Pink?!
自汽车发明以来  怎么没人
Once cars were invented, why didn't they just
把马都杀了  用车撞死
kill all the horses. With the cars?
多读读书吧傻子
Beat it Summer School.
小马直升机来袭  不倒下就炸死
Horse-a-copter attack! It' s plops or bomb
放开她  她是我的救赎  而且对男人过敏
Let her go, She's a rescue and uneasy around men.
我的小围场
My paddock!
不准玩马
No horse play.
玩马
Horse play.
马姬  你猜我刚才说了句啥  接着打
Marge, guess whaI said. Fight on.
为什么  为什么你总是要毁掉我在意的东西
Why? Why do you always wreck the stuff I care about?
大哥哥应该善良又乐于助人
Big brothers are supposed to be helpful and a little nice.
真希望没你这个哥哥
I wish I could un-brother you.
是我没你这种妹妹才对
Not if I un-sister you first.
好吧  以安全剪刀赐予我的权利
Fine. By the power of safety scissors,
我在此解除兄妹关系
I hereby sever the sibling bond.
一刀两断
Snip.
看看这大房子
Look at that house.
我猜他们的车库肯定是用来停车的
I bet they use their garage for cars.
小马的生日
Horsey birthday!
你的家好大
Your house is huge.
是啊  还有点尴尬
Yeah, it's kind of embarrassing.
我爸爸是番茄酱供应商
My dad's the exclusive ketchup distributor
独家给体育场和大型教堂供货
for stadiums and megachurches.
她显然是在撒谎  番茄酱是免费的
She's obviously lying. Ketchup is free.
赠品
Play along.
你好  我是马姬
Hi, I'm Marge.
丽莎一直很期待来参加你女儿的派对
Lisa's really been looking forward to your daughter's party.
不不  我是派对策划员
Oh, no, I'm the party planner.
她妈妈为了让儿子进南加州大学正在修图呢
The mother's on a photoshopping retreat to get her son into USC.
玩的开心  明天见
Have fun. We'll see you tomorrow.
上午十点来接  再见  拿礼品袋
10:00 a.m. pickup. Goodbyes and gift bags.
他们太有钱了  能预知未来
They're so rich, they know the future.
我刚刚读完《赛马少女》这本书
Well, I just finished the Gallop Girls book
乔治·华盛顿的马背叛了本尼迪克特·阿诺德的马
where George Washington's horse exposed Benedict Arnold's horse
它是个叛徒
as a traitor.
我还想把这作为惊喜呢
I kind of wanted it to be a surprise.
马好像是我们的
We kind of own horses.
丽萨去朋友家过夜  爷爷看着那两个孩子
You know, Lisa has a sleepover, Grampa's with the other ones,
我们在码头附近
and we are near the marina.
我才不去找你弄丢的墨镜
I'm not looking for your lost sunglasses.
已经六年了  早没了
It's been six years. They're gone.
你总是说我从不会做计划
You are always saying how I never make plans for us.
不如我们来一趟落日巡游吧
Well, how about a sunset cruise?
我之前只在《黄昏游》杂志看到过
I only ever read about those in Sunset Cruise magazine.
这里甚至还有现场演奏
There's even live music.
快乐水手乐队主唱
这个乐队本来是要在莱尼的婚礼上演唱的
This is the band that was gonna play Lenny's wedding reception
只可惜他在圣坛上喷洒胡椒
if he didn't get pepper-sprayed at the altar.
我都快忘了
I forgot how handsome you are
你出一点点力的时候有多帅
when you make the slightest effort.
别担心
Don't worry.
如果你被甩出去  你的背心会自动充气
If you get thrown, your vest will automatically inflate
这样你就不会被摔到
so it breaks your fall.
现在用你的缰绳
Now use the reins.
向日葵想让你带领她
Sunflower wants you to lead her.
怎么回事  艾迪森  你不喜欢我的推文
What's the matter, Addison? You didn't like my post.
你的大拇指废了吗
Is your thumb broken?
大拇指废了
Thumb broken?
泰莎·萝丝  你真是太优秀了  十分优秀
Tessa Rose, you are brills. Completely brills.
说真的  这是有史以来最好笑的事
Literally, that was the funniest thing ever.
我忍不住笑了出来
I can't stop laughing.
艾迪森  为什么她盯着我们
Addison, why is she staring at us?
艾迪森
Addision? ‭
你喜欢这样的称呼吗
Is that what you like to be called?
这是我的伙伴
This is my crew.
你可能在社交网络上都认识她们
You probably know them all from social.
这是贝拉·艾拉  富二代  聚友网认识的
This is Bella-Ella. She's from old money. Myspace.
美国在线社交网站
斯隆  英国人
Sloan. British.
还有美女偶像泰莎·萝丝
And, of course, beauty icon Tessa Rose.
你们不讨厌她吗
Don't you just hate her?
对了  各位  这是丽莎
Oh, right, uh, guys, this is Lisa.
-她就是她  -很高兴见到大家
- She's... her. - Nice to meet you, guys.
你要冷静
Um, you need to calm down.
我很冷静
I am calm.
-别喊了  -我没喊
- Stop yelling. - I'm not yelling.
听着  衣着单调的你
Look, matchy-matchy,
我不需要和一些
I don't need drama from someone
身上的衣服和裤子不搭的人有交集
whose shirt is a spoiler for her pants.
你真幽默  我笑得停不下来
You're hilarious. I will never stop laughing.
你的朋友看起来和你不太一样
Your friends seem, um, different than you.
那个人一直说很搞笑  但是她都不笑出来
That one keeps saying things are funny, but she's not laughing.
肉毒素可以麻痹肌肉来除皱
她笑不出  她妈妈怀孕时打了太多的肉毒素
Oh, she can't. Her mom got too much Botox when she was pregnant.
太幸运了
Ugh, so lucky.
我知道她们看起来既排外又高傲还很
I know they seem cliquey and stuck-up and...
-讨厌  -对
- Awful? - Yeah.
但一旦她们接受了你
But once they accept you,
你会觉得其实她们  挺好的
you'll see that, deep down,they're... nice.
那就好那就好  不刻薄就好
Oh, good, good. So they're not mean.
我差点给她们贴标签了
Oh, I almost judged them.
真险
That was close.
正好遮我的康普茶黑眼圈
These will totally hide my kombucha hangovers.
我在市里买的  纽约市
I got them in the city.The city is New York.
纽约市哦
New York City?
我会记下来  记在本上  笔记本哦
I'll make a note, in a book. A notebook.
手机壳
A phone case.
最新款麦疯的壳
It's for the new MyPhone.
那手机没按键  摄像头只单朝向你
There's no buttons, and the camera only faces you.
就是字面意义的没用
It's literally unusable.
看看我的礼物
What about my gift?
还有一顶小草帽
Look, it's got a little straw hat
正能套上他的耳朵
that fits right over his ears.
她送了个玩具
She got her a toy.
带尿布吗
Does it come with a nappy?
我的天  我笑到不行
Oh, my God, I'm laughing so hard,
都没法喘气了
I can't even breathe.
古铜色是化妆品还是卸妆水  怎么涂
Does it dispense bronzer? Bronzer remover? What does it dispense?
怎么涂颜色
How is it makeup?
但你喜欢  对不对阿迪
But you like it, don't you, Addy?
很可爱
Oh, it's... adorable.
对尿裤子的小孩来说
For a "widdle" baby.
快乐水手乐队
丽莎·辛普森
聪明的那个
信号不好  宝贝
You're breaking up, honey.
派对怎么样啊
How's the party?
不好玩  我不想待在这了
It's not fun. I don't want to stay.
我想回家
I want to go home.
很好玩
It's... fun.
我不想回家
I don't want to... go home.
谢谢你多余的炫耀
Thanks for the uneventful update.
丽莎怎么样
How's Lisa?
玩得挺开心不想回家
Having fun and not wanting to go home.
不错呀
Sounds like fun.
你  没  明白  过来  现在
你  明白  现在
没错  爸爸明白得很
You're right. Daddy understands completely.
爸爸们就是这样的
That's what daddies do.
你  没  明白  过来  现在
我今晚被困在这里了
I'm trapped. All night.
和她们一起
With them.
你说泰勒·斯威夫特仿妆取消了
What do you mean the Taylor Swift lookalike canceled?
那现在女孩子们朝谁扔纸杯蛋糕啊
Now who are the girls gonna throw cupcakes at?
终于  你是这里唯一的大人
Finally. You're the only adult here.
我想回家  帮帮我好吗
I want to go home. Can you help me?
不行  过夜是要从头待到尾的
Oh, no, this sleepover has got to get 100% engagement.
我不能回布巴甘虾业公司上班
I can't go back to working at Bubba Gump Shrimp.
他们卖的不是虾
It's not shrimp.
尊贵的小姐们
Hey, lady bosses,
你们愿意走进香水实验室
who wants to visit the perfume lab
打造自己的香氛吗
and start your own fempire?
你用的是哪款香  饥渴老女人的绝望香吗
What are you wearing, Desperation by Thirsty Grandma?
我二十六岁
I'm 26.
我们一起刷新一季的《感谢上帝我死了》吧
Let's binge the new season of Thank God I'm Dead.
《感上我死》真是鸿篇巨制
T.G. I'm. D is literally massive.
伦德拉的葬礼在我的愿景板占有一席之地
Leandra's funeral is so on my vision board.
我不被允许看这个节目
I'm not allowed to watch that show
因为它在美化不当的行为
'cause it glamorizes inappropriateness.
没关系的  闭上眼就行了
It'll be okay. Just close your eyes.
警告  以下内容不适合青少年  儿童  和成年人观看
有可能导致噩梦和夜惊
本节目分类标签为
"恐怖""困扰"及"糟糕透顶"
警告
我们懂了  警告们  这个节目棒极了
We get it, warnings, this show is awesome.
天地明鉴
她去世了  也终于出名了
Now that she's gone, she's finally popular.
我要邀请她的鬼魂去舞会
I'm gonna ask her ghost to the prom.
有人要火了
Someone's about to go viral.
有关宝宝的视频最流行了
Baby videos are super popular.
泰莎·萝丝的圈子
#丽莎宝宝
你在这里干什么  这是餐饮人员的洗手间
What are you doing in here? This is the caterers' bathroom.
这个日式马桶是今晚我听到的
This Japanese toilet is the first kind voice
第一个和善的声音
I've heard all night.
未识别到屁股
阿迪  你为什么邀请我  为了折磨我吗
Addy, why did you invite me to this party? Just to torture me?
好吧  告诉你  我邀请你
Okay. Full disclosure, I invited you
是因为她们对我总是很刻薄
because those other girls are always so mean to me.
现在被欺负的是你  我就可以加入她们了
But then they were mean to you instead and let me join in.
谢谢你让我过上最棒的生日
Oh, thanks for making this the best birthday ever.
不对  这太恶毒了
Wait, no "Aw." That's horrible.
你还不明白吗
No, don't you see?
下次你再带个丽莎
Next time, you bring a Lisa.
乐队夏令营或科学俱乐部里的人
Someone from band camp or science club or whatever,
我们一起攻击她  你就可以加入组织了
and then we'll all turn on her and you'll be part of the squad.
你不可能是这样的人
No, no. No, this can't be who you really are.
让我帮你美白牙齿吧  丽莎  我有牙贴
Let me whiten your teeth, Lisa. I've got strips.
牙贴  丽莎  快回来  这可是美白牙贴啊
Strips, Lisa! Lisa, come back! I've got whitening strips!
欢迎来到老头五百英里大奖赛现场
And it's the Old-Man-apolis 500,
选手脱轨了  一头栽进亡者臀沟
but he spun out into Dead Man's Crack.
爷爷  我是丽莎
Grampa, it's Lisa.
-我需要你的帮助  -什么事  蠢货
- I need your help. - What's the matter, loser?
是不是马咬掉了你的头  你因为没有头
Did a horse bite your head off, and now you're crying
在伤心哭泣
because you don't have a head?
说中了
Ha! Called it.
这个派对上的女孩们太刻薄了
The girls at this party are so mean.
没人能帮我  我想回家
there's no one else to help me, and I just want to go home.
我非常想帮你  可惜你和我断绝关系了
Oh, I would love to help, but you un-brothered me.
我现在只是磁化了你的萨克斯的陌生人
Now all I am is a stranger who magnetized your saxophone.
拜托了  你的内心深处
Please, somewhere inside you
一定还残留着我们之间纽带的微弱火星
there is an ember of connection between us.
求求你点燃这颗火星吧
This is me asking you to fan that ember.
重新打一次  好好说话
Call me back and say it in a normal way.
快来解救老娘
Get me out of here!
快看  怪咖在打电话呢
Look, the rando's talking into a phone.
手机是拿来看的  呆子
Phones are for looking at, rando.
巴仔  她们在抢我的手机
Bart, they're taking my phone.
她们甚至比你还坏
They're even meaner than you.
胡安·斯塔诺提普吗[谐音"一星无小费"]
Are you Juan Starnotip?
开你的车
Just drive.
胡安  今晚什么打算
So, Juan, going somewhere this evening?
去输入的地址
The entered address.
我喜欢你  胡安  你一看就自信自在
I like you, Juan. You're clearly comfortable in your own skin.
我能请你喝常温的气泡水吗
Can I interest you in a room-temperature sparkling water?
别交流
I requested no conversation.
请给司机打星  一星差评
还给我
Give it back!
这只手机是赛百味做的
This phone is made by Subway.
我爸吃了一千个三十厘米三明治才拿到的
My dad had to eat a thousand footlongs for that!
别勾引我老婆  你个只会哼唱的色海盗
Quit hitting on my wife, you crooning sex pirate.
那个蓝发夫人背后的小妞是你老婆吗
That chick behind that blue-haired lady's your wife?
厉害了
Way to go, man.
好吧
Oh, right, uh,
我让你过去
I'll just get out of your way.
这下是为你不勾引我老婆
This is for not hitting on my wife.
-歌单  -我们的段子都在上面
- The set list. - Our banter is on there.
我们会什么歌
What songs do we know?
没了酒  这就只是普通航程了
Without the booze, it's just a cruise!
伙计  你毁了音乐
Dude, you killed the music.
还有气氛  死亡时间  晚上10时30分
And the vibe. Time of death: 10:30 pm.
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
在她们发现我走了之前  我们快溜
Now let's get out of here before they realize I'm going.
这次派对还没结束
This sleepover isn't over.
结束了  我们一走就算结束了
No, yes, it is. When we leave, it's over.
我来不是为了救你
Look, I didn't come here to rescue you.
你要是现在逃了  你以后永远都只会逃避
If you run now, you'll never stop running.
什么意思
What do you mean?
你还要给那些小富婆们一份礼物
There's one present you still have to give those rich girls.
-复仇  -复仇
- Revenge. - Revenge?
泰莎·萝丝的圈子
#煞风景
复仇
Revenge.
好了  复仇  我可以的
Okay, right. Revenge. Right. I can do that.
-我要怎么做  -不能由我来说
‭- What do I do? - I can't tell you.
真正的复仇只能由你心中的恨意产生
True revenge can only come from the hate in your own heart.
恨意
Hate.
如果编得够紧  就像是做了面部拉皮
If you do it tight enough, it's just like a face-lift.
天啊  我都能被当作六岁了
Oh, my God. I could pass for six.
我知道要怎么做了
I know just what to do.
蹄硬化剂
喂  妈妈
Hi, Mom.
我看到你打来好几次  没出什么事吧
I saw you called a bunch of times. Is everything okay?
是的  一切都好  我爱你  晚安
Yeah, everything is great. I love you, good night.
至少她玩得很开心
At least she's having fun.
你的莫斯艾斯利噪音已经完全扼杀了
Your Mos Eisley fracas has utterly harshed
星战系列作品中的城市  由沙漠发展而来
我的阿拉肯香料潮流
my Arrakeen spice buzz.
美国科幻文学《沙丘》中的虚构沙漠城市  盛产香料
没错  这是一句有两处引用的控诉
That's right, a two-reference complaint!
我和我妻子已经期待这个好几个月了
My wife and I have been looking forward to this for months,
-而你破坏了我们的计划  -没错
- and you ruined our plans. - Yeah.
计划  对  我们都爱制定计划  不是吗
Plans? Yeah, we all love to make plans, don't we?
晚餐和电影  情侣K歌  游戏之夜
Dinner and a movie, couples' karaoke, game night
虽然举办者们只是想推销安利产品
where the hosts are really just trying to sell Amway.
安利
我们都很想走出家门
We're all so eager to get out of the house.
不过是为什么呢
But why?
是为了用棍子举着小胡子  站在线内
To stand in line to have your picture taken
拍张照片吗
holding a mustache on a stick?
这些梦幻的计划都是为了浪漫
And all these magical plans are supposed to lead up to romance.
可当你回到家  你觉得疲倦又恶心
But when you get home, you feel tired and gross
觉得自己老到走不动路
and a thousand years old.
于是你为一个又一个夜晚制定计划
So you make plans for another night and another,
这种循环永不停歇  而你唯一触碰
and the cycle continues until the only time
你妻子的时候  就是你没注意她凌晨四点
you touch your wife is when you don't notice
坐在马桶上  而你一屁股坐在了她身上
she's on the toilet at 4:00 A.M. and you sit on her.
我没有毁掉这次航行
I didn't ruin this cruise.
我拯救了你们的生活
I saved your life.
现在回家去  不要再制定计划了
Now return to your homes and never make plans again.
那个呆子弄乱了我们的头发
That egghead rando messed with our hair.
我们跟她看起来差不多了
We look like her!
别担心  外面有车等着我们
Don't worry. I have a car waiting.
峰时价格的接机服务
An airport pickup during surge pricing?
再见  点阵式打印机  你好  喷墨式打印机
So long, dot matrix printer, hello, bubble jet.
这边
This way.
你上吧
You go ahead.
你不是讨厌马
You don't hate horses.
你是怕它们
You're afraid of them.
不是  我只是讨厌和警察一起工作的动物
No, I'm not. I-I just hate any animal that works with cops.
动物的性子不该那么烈
No creature should be that jacked.
我害怕的时候你可没让我退缩
You didn't let me quit when I was scared,
所以我要让你见识一下
so I'm gonna help you see
这匹威风的生物有着温柔的灵魂
that this majestic creature has a gentle soul.
别站在她身后  她会把你的脸踢掉的
Not behind her! She'll kick your face off!
我们要把你的图享  抖音和外卖软件毁掉
We're gonna destroy you on Insta, TikTok and Postmates.
你会成为社交网络的弃儿  还得自提寿司
You'll be a total outcast and you'll have to pick up your own sushi.
这里没有WiFi吗
Ugh, no Wi-Fi?
你的马有移动热点吗  艾迪森
Does your horse even have a mobile hot spot, Addison?
艾迪森  我能和艾迪聊聊吗  我的读书伙伴
Addison, can I talk to Addy, my book buddy?
我必须得是艾迪森
Hmm, I have to be Addison.
艾迪只是个小女孩
Addy's just a little girl.
你不记得我们一起读这本书的时候了吗
Don't you remember when we were reading this?
我们那时只是孩子  分享着喜欢的东西
We were just kids, sharing something we loved.
艾迪森  她想给你洗脑
Addison, she's trying to influence you,
而且她都不是为了钱
and she's not even monetizing it.
我一定要在圣诞节早上匿名举报她家
I'm so going to swat her house on Christmas morning.
别让那个呆子烦你了
Don't let that rando upset you.
吃个抗焦虑的口香糖吧
Have a Klonopin gummy.
做回那个我认识的女孩吧
Be the girl I know you are.
旧书的味道
Old book smell.
别拿着书了  艾迪森  你跟个呆子一样
Stop holding a book, Addison. You're acting like a rando.
我叫艾迪
My name is Addy.
我的...
Oh, my...
快跑
Go!
跟我们走吧  这里没什么值得你留恋的了
Come with us. There's nothing left for you here.
这是我家  我的东西都在这里
It's my house. All my stuff is in it.
对  对  好吧
Oh, right, right. Well, all right.
或许我们可以在图书馆再见
Maybe I'll see you at the library.
丽莎
Lisa?
你是我最好的礼物
You were my best gift.
艾迪森  你疯了吗
Addison, are you out of your mind?
网飞该拍一部关于你社交生活的连续剧
Netflix should make a series about your social life,
因为它刚刚自杀身亡了
because it just committed suicide.
她真够坏的
She is so mean.
我想跟她做朋友
I want to be her friend.
真的
Literally.